- question: "When running an Ad-Hoc Ansible command, you are running Ansible without a _______ :"
  answers:
  - "ansible.cfg"
  - "inventory file"
  - "playbook"
  - "module"
  correct: "playbook"
  day: 2

- question: "What file lists connection info (IP address, user name) for hosts and groups of hosts?"
  answers:
  - "playbook"
  - "module"
  - "inventory"
  - "ansible.cfg"
  correct: "inventory"
  day: 2

- question: "If you wanted to set a default location for where Ansible looks for your inventory file, where would you add that rule?"
  answers:
  - "playbook"
  - "module"
  - "inventory"
  - "ansible.cfg"
  correct: "ansible.cfg"
  day: 2

- question: "List the following from LARGEST to SMALLEST:"
  answers:
  - "Plays, Playbooks, Tasks"
  - "Tasks, Playbooks, Plays"
  - "Playbooks, Plays, Tasks"
  correct: "Playbooks, Plays, Tasks"
  day: 2

- question: "In an Ansible playbook, what section contains tasks and is executed in order?"
  answers:
  - "pre_tasks"
  - "post_tasks"
  - "tasks"
  - "handlers"
  correct: "tasks"
  day: 2

- question: "The raw, shell, and command modules all fail idempotence. What is idempotence in Ansible?"
  answers:
  - "Makes a change the first time ONLY"
  - "Makes a change every time."
  - "Throws an error if a change must be made more than once."
  correct: "Makes a change every time."
  day: 3

- question: "Uh oh! Your host doesn't have Python installed! What module will you likely use to automate installing Python on hosts?"
  answers:
  - "apt"
  - "yum"
  - "raw"
  - "lineinfile"
  correct: "raw"
  day: 3

- question: "When you use a LOOP, what is the variable that represents each item being returned from the loop?"
  answers:
  - "x"
  - "item"
  - "element"
  - "state"
  correct: "item"
  day: 3

- question: "What keyword allows us to set a condition that must be met before a task runs?"
  answers:
  - "if"
  - "try"
  - "when"
  - "check"
  correct: "when"
  day: 3

- question: "What’s the primary purpose of putting tags on tasks?"
  answers:
  - "Adding metadata identifying what that task does"
  - "Allows selection of what tasks do and do not run"
  - "Gives the task a name to differentiate between other tasks"
  correct: "Allows selection of what tasks do and do not run"
  day: 4

- question: "When does a handler task run?"
  answers:
  - "Every time the 'tasks' section finishes."
  - "Only when notified by a task."
  - "Only when notified by a task AND that task created a change/turned yellow."
  - "Before the 'tasks' section begins."
  correct: "Only when notified by a task AND that task created a change/turned yellow."
  day: 4

- question: "When you’re looking to

 download a new 'toolkit' full of additional modules, you will likely download a _____:"
  answers:
  - "Role"
  - "Collection"
  - "Ansible Galaxy"
  correct: "Collection"
  day: 4

- question: "What is ansible-vault?"
  answers:
  - "An encryption tool for files or strings that teams use for their playbooks."
  - "A storage tool that makes playbooks reusable by teams"
  - "A security tool that hides files so they are only detectable by the playbook."
  correct: "An encryption tool for files or strings that teams use for their playbooks."
  day: 5

- question: "The Ansible controller that runs against a Dell EMC PowerEdge server would need the OMSDK installed via pip and the 'dellemc.openmanage' collection installed. What would the hosts/connection be in that playbook?"
  answers:
  - "dellemc, http"
  - "localhost, local"
  - "openmanage, ssh"
  - "dellemc, network_cli"
  correct: "dellemc, network_cli"
  day: 5

- question: "Why must we use a network_cli connection when using Ansible to configure most network devices?"
  answers:
  - "network devices can't receive SSH commands"
  - "expect scripting is inefficient, so we don't use it"
  - "network devices' OS doesn't permit Python to be installed"
  - "because everything has to be SO DARN DIFFICULT these days"
  correct: "network devices' OS doesn't permit Python to be installed"
  day: 5

- question: "Which tool is commonly used as an open-source automation server for building, deploying, and automating projects?"
  day: 5
  answers:
    - GitLab
    - Bamboo
    - Travis CI
    - Jenkins
  correct: "Jenkins"

- question: "Which Ansible collection provides advanced modules and roles for automating DellEMC storage arrays?"
  day: 5
  answers:
    - Microsoft Azure (azure)
    - Kubernetes (kubernetes)
    - Palo Alto Networks (paloaltonetworks)
    - DellEMC (dellemc)"
  correct: "DellEMC (dellemc)"
